// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "At noon, johnny went for his grandparents' house for __________",
    answer: "lunch",
    options: [
      "lunch",
      "breakfast",
      "dinner",
      "supper"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The cake was so _________ that thirty people could eat it.",
    answer: "big",
    options: [
      "big",
      "small",
      "tiny",
      "heavy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Father wanted to ________ some peanut butter on the bread with a knife.",
    answer: "spread",
    options: [
      "spread",
      "scooped",
      "sprinkled",
      "shake"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The _________ can fly?",
    answer: "bird",
    options: [
      "bird",
      "lion",
      "kangaroo",
      "elephant"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The sheep and its _______ were playing in the field.",
    answer: "lamb",
    options: [
      "calf",
      "foal",
      "lamb",
      "parrot"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Walking through the ________, mary saw a monkey on top of a tree.",
    answer: "jungle",
    options: [
      "river",
      "jungle",
      "tunnel",
      "road"
    ]
  },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Ken and I ________ best friends. We always play together.",
        answer: "are",
        options: [
        "were",
        "are",
        "is",
        "am"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "The chef added _________ cheese to the pizza",
        answer: "some",
        options: [
        "a few",
        "some",
        "many",
        "tiny"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Last night, my brother ____________ off his bed and injured his foot",
        answer: "jumped",
        options: [
          "jumps",
          "jumped",
          "jumping",
          "hopping"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Eat healthily _______ you may fall sick, said mother.",
        answer: "or",
        options: [
          "or",
          "so",
          "and",
          "may"
        ]
      },
      {
      numb: 11,
      question: "We should not look directly at ________ sun as the strong rays will hurt our eyes.",
      answer: "the",
      options: [
        "the",
        "a",
        "an",
        "and"
      ]
    },
        {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Ali is playing with his new toy. _______ is having fun",
        answer: "he",
        options: [
        "she",
        "I",
        "It",
        "he"
        ]
    },
  
];